众议院唱名投票选举
The House will come to order for a roll call vote
2017年1月3日
国会投票选举美国总统
美国总统的会议现在开始
on the matter of who will be the President of the United States.
来自亚利桑那的威廉·奥布莱恩议员...
Senator William O'Brien from Arizona...
好了 开始了 阿拉巴马在字母表里排第一
All right, here we go. Alabama first in the alphabet,
其他方面就是吊车尾
last in every other fucking thing.
我倒是相信它在谋杀黑人之后最容易
I believe it's number one in easiest state
- 逍遥法外的州里排第一 - 拜托
- to get away with murdering a black guy. - Come on, come on.
阿拉巴马投票给赛琳娜·梅耶副总统
Alabama casts its vote for President Selina Meyer.
这才是好城市!
That's my town!
太棒了... 凯瑟琳
Yeah... Catherine.
你就不能把相机放下一会吗?
Would you please give it a rest with that camera?
我叫凯瑟琳·梅耶
My name is Catherine Meyer.
梅耶国会竞选
胜利庆祝会
十点新闻
我的一生都在被人关注
I've spent my entire life in the public eye.
民众会一直记得
While the public will always remember me as the little girl
我小时候在一晚上掉下两次舞台
who fell off the stage twice in one evening,
现在我是个成熟的女人了 拥有自己的激情与兴趣
I'm a grown woman now with my own passions and interests.
"无声的罪恶//基斯顿输油管项目"
凯瑟琳 梅耶编舞
瓦萨学院 2013级
在我以及整个家庭的生活中
One of the biggest things that ever happened in my life
发生过的最大的事就是140年以来
and my family's life happened when the House of Representatives
众议院第一次投票
voted to decide the presidency of the United States
来选举美国总统
for the first time in 140 years.
在那天的两个月前
Almost two months to the day earlier,
选举日|2016年11月8日
美国人民为总统大选进行了投票
the American people voted for president,
但那晚以比尔·奥布莱恩议员
but that night ended in an historic electoral college tie
纽约 2016年11月9日 星期三
选举人团僵持不定 总统大选悬而未决
历史性的平局后公众提问
值得铭记
的一夜
两位候选人
最亲近的一夜
突发新闻
选举人团何去何从
总统职位暂未确定
与现任副总统赛琳娜·梅耶
between Senator Bill O'Brien
也就是我妈妈之间的历史性的平局结束
and the sitting president Selina Meyer, my mom.
这意味着众议院
It meant that the House of Representatives
国会
个州参与投票
需要投票打破平局并选出新任总统
needed to vote to break the tie and choose a president.
票赢得选举
我保龄球教练说过 平局就像亲你的姐妹一样
My bowling coach used to say a tie was like kissing your sister.
是吗 那这个就像我的姐妹在我胸口便便了一样
Yeah, well, this feels like my sister took a shit on my chest.
姐妹之吻
凯瑟琳 梅耶制作
平局的故事
为了讲好这个故事
In order to tell this story,
2016年11月9日
距国会投票55天
我得回到一切刚开始的地方
I have to go back to where it all began,
总统大选平局之后那天
the day after the presidential election was tied.
苏 威尔逊 莱文森
总统梅耶的私人助理
我绝不同意我的肖像
I do not give my consent to have my likeness
出现在这个以及其他任何影片中
appear in this or any other film.
总统现在可以见你了
The president will see you now.
我打算拍一部关于这次平局的影片
I set out to make a film about the tie,
但在这过程之中
but somewhere along the way,
我最终探索到了一些关于自己的事情
I ended up discovering something about myself.
我要检查所有的影片
I'm gonna have to have approval over
凯瑟琳 明白吗?
all of this footage, Catherine, okay?
好的 我们一会再谈这个
Okay, we can talk about that after.
你第一次想成为总统是什么时候?
When did you first know that you wanted to be president?
那是1973年
It was 1973.
- 凯瑟琳 出去 - 我还是个小女孩
- Catherine, out. - I was a very little girl
母亲当时"不舒服"
and Mother wasn't "Feeling well."
赛琳娜 梅耶
美国总统
爸爸邀请我在尼克松的
Daddy asked me to be his date
就职舞会上做他的舞伴
for President Nixon's inaugural ball.
爸爸和碧碧·雷博佐有很多生意来往
Daddy did a lot of business with Bebe Rebozo.
当尼克松总统走进房间时
President Nixon entered the room
他戴着领结 他的眉毛
and, you know, he had his bow tie and his eyebrows.
我爸俯身和我说
Daddy leaned in to me and he said,
"你知道吗 很多人不喜欢尼克松
"You know, a lot of people don't like Nixon,
但上帝作证 他们都尊重他
but by God, they respect him.
你也会是这样 小花生"
And that's you, peanut."
2017年1月3日
国会投票日
- 特拉华州? - 快点 快点
- Delaware? - Come on, come on.
梅耶:4   奥布莱恩:3
特拉华州投票支持赛琳娜·梅耶副总统
Delaware votes for President Selina Meyer.
我不想触霉头 各位
I don't want to jinx things, guys,
不过我觉得也许我们该列张我胜利之后
but I think maybe we should start making our list
要惩罚谁的名单了
of who I'm going to punish when I win.
- 你在哪呢? - 我不知道
- Where are you? - I don't know.
昨晚我和一个国会的粉丝女孩一起回家
I went home with a congressional fan girl last night.
我的车没了 我觉得我在马里兰
I don't have my car. I think I'm in Maryland.
先生 首先得祝贺你
Well, first of all, sir, congratulations are in order.
她养了只操蛋的鹦鹉 要是鹦鹉醒了
She's got a fucking parrot, and if the parrot wakes up,
绝对会把她妈吵醒
the parrot's gonna make noise and wake up her mom.
- 投票开始了吗? - 是的 特拉华刚刚投了票
- Has the vote started yet? - Yes, Delaware just voted.
妈的 妈的 好吧 你过来接我
Shit. Shit. Okay, you gotta come get me.
好的 你先在苹果地图上定个位...
Okay, just drop a pin in Apple Maps and...
我他妈不会定位
I don't know how to drop a fucking pin.
这功能很简单
Well, it's a really intuitive feature.
- 你是IOS 9.2.3的系统吗? - 闭嘴吧
- Do you have iOS 9.2.3? - Shut up.
给我带一套衣服然后来接我
Bring me a change of clothes and come and get me.
平局之后的那天 股市崩盘了
The day after the tie, the stock markets crashed,
汤姆 詹姆斯:新经济重臣
不过我妈尽了全力来挽救
but my mom did everything she could to get them back on track.
今天下午 我问了汤姆·詹姆斯
This afternoon, I asked Tom James
是否能为他的国家
to do his country the
而任职经济重臣
honor of stepping up to serve as economy czar
让我非常高兴的是 他同意了
and to my absolute delight, he said yes.
你运动过吗?
Did you ever play sports?
还记得没有人愿意当接球手吗?
Remember how no one ever wanted to play catcher?
接球手就有点像经济重臣的感觉
Playing catcher is kind of like being the economy czar.
参议员 汤姆 詹姆斯
副总统候选人 经济重臣
没多少荣耀 还要一直蹲伏着
There's not a lot of glory, but a lot of squatting.
一堆人对你指手画脚
A lot of asses in your face.
非常感谢你
Thank you so much,
- 詹姆斯议员 - 你太客气了
- Senator James. - You're very welcome.
- 进行的怎么样? - 非常好 谢谢你
- How's it going? - It's going very well, thanks.
- 鲍勃是你叔叔 - 敲一敲 未来的召唤
- And Bob's your uncle. - Knock, knock, future calling.
天啊 拜托了 路易丝
Cheese, please, Louise.
先生们 你们认识第一女儿吧
Gentlemen, you know the first daughter.
- 当然 - 她在为大学课题而采访我
- We do. - She's interviewing me for a college project.
不 是博士课题
No, it's a doc.
那种专门给喜欢哭丧着脸的人们拍的影片
Yeah, like one of those movies for people who like to be sad.
你对选举平局有什么看法?
What do you think of the electoral tie?
有一天晚上我好不容易闭上了眼睛
You know, at night when I dare to close my eyes,
比尔 艾瑞克森
白宫前通信主管
我梦到你母亲输掉了
I dream about your mother losing
然后又突然在高速公路出口坡道下
and then coming upon her holding a cardboard sign
遇见她举着硬纸板指示牌
at the bottom of a highway exit ramp.
如果我是汤姆·詹姆斯
Now, if I were Tom James,
我就直接弄到三个州
I would just try to get three states to
然后弃权去参议院
abstain and then it would go to the Senate,
为美国历史上
serving the president the most abject humiliation
最难堪耻辱的总统服务
in the history of the United States.
你知道硬纸板牌子上写了什么吗?
You know what the cardboard sign says?
写了什么?
What does it say?
写着 "我太抱歉了 比尔·艾瑞克森"
It says, "I'm so sorry, Bill Ericsson."
如果你落选了会怎么办?
What if you lose the presidency?
让我告诉你
Well, I'll tell you something,
你不能这么想
you can't think that way.
我妈总是这么说
That's what Mother always said.
当你有消极的情绪时
When you have those kinds of negative feelings,
你就把它们捡起来塞进盒子里
you just pick them up and you stuff them in your box
再把盒子紧紧关上
and you close it down tight and you take that box
把盒子推到最里面...
and you shove it way back here in your...
脑袋的角落里 再把钥匙吞掉
in the corner of your head and swallow that key.
然后它们一下子就不见了
And then, poof, they're gone.
就是这样 它确实管用 宝贝
And then that's it. And it works, too, sweetie.
这是我妈说过管用的方法
That's something that Mother told me that works.
把热水倒进壶里 没问题吧?
Okay, you pour the hot water into the pot, all right?
盖瑞 沃尔什
总统梅耶的特别助理和私人助手
稍微晃一晃
Swirl it around a bit.
再把热水倒出去 好吗?
And then you pour it out, okay?
这就叫给壶预热
That's called hot in the pot.
现在这个是我的招牌混合茶
Now this is a special blend I've got.
里面有洋甘菊 蔷薇果
It's got chamomile and rose hips
以及其它一些我不会在镜头面前
and some other little special ingredients
告诉你的特殊的配方
that I'm not gonna tell you on camera.
我的问题是
My question was
你对金融危机有什么看法
what's your take on the financial crisis.
我就是觉得他们钱不够了
I just think they ran out of money.
他们应该再印一些出来
They should probably just print more.
我不懂这算什么大问题
I don't know why it's been such a big issue.
好了 各位 话说我们什么时候炒了麦克?
Okay, guys, when are we gonna fire Mike, by the way?
他真是操蛋事不断啊
Because it is seriously just one fuckup after fuckup with him.
是啊 就职典礼之后
Yeah, right after the inauguration,
我们就把麦克屎托克先生请出门去
we'll show Mr. McShittock the door.
我热爱自己的工作
I love my job.
迈克 麦克林托克
白宫新闻发言人
上帝 我想永远做下去
Oh, my God, I want to do it forever.
尤其这份工作
Especially because this is the kind of job
每年都可以让我不断进步
that I've gotten better at every year.
而且工作时
And it's also the kind of job
你必须办事迅速
that you need to be fast on your feet.
要雷厉风行 还有就是那种
You need to be quick and you need to sort of,
我词穷了
uh, I don't even know what the word is.
我们现在正忙着把客房改造成育儿室
We're in the process of converting the guest bedroom
迎接来自中国的小天使
into a nursery for our arriving Chinese angel.
在这儿我们贴了个山寨小熊维尼
We went with a Winnie the Pooh knockoff.
中国制造 可以给埃伦营造家的感觉
It's made in China so Ellen will feel right at home.
我想他是叫"快乐太阳熊"
I think he's called Happy Sun Bear.
比美国的便宜多了 我们还检测了屋子含铅量
So much cheaper. And we've checked the room for lead,
我要... 应该是我来检测
so there's... actually, I need... I'm supposed to check...
我得找个人检测这屋子的含铅量
I have to get a guy to check the room for lead,
我们一定会查的
but we will check for lead.
突发新闻
内华达重新计票 有望助力梅耶当选总统
11月中旬 我母亲的竞选团队
In mid-November, my mom's team
质疑内华达州的总票数
challenged the vote totals in Nevada,
肯特 戴维森
竞选经理
这意味着平局或许将被打破
which meant the tie might not be a tie any longer.
- 我改主意了 - 关于什么?
- I've changed my mind. - About what?
派我去内华达吧 我想去
Send me to Nevada. I want the job.
可是凯蒂·卡罗索也想去
Oh, but so does Candi Caruso.
而且 尽管如此 她说
And even though, and I quote,
我是个女人 这一事实
the fact that I'm a woman
意味着我们再也不会有其他女总统了
means we will no longer have any women presidents
因为我们尝试过了 但她太坑爹了
because we've already tried one and she fucking sucked.
求你了 求求你
Please, please, please.
好吧 我可以告诉你这点..
Well, I'll give you this...
凯蒂·卡罗索才不会去给这堆烂事擦屁股
Candi Caruso would not eat this amount of shit.
除非她之后跑到浴室隔间
Unless afterward she went into a bathroom stall
用的还是老式的两指木片切削机
and used the old two-fingered wood chipper.
如果可以选择你
Why would I want to stand next to a twig
我怎么会想跟那样的弱鸡去虚度光阴呢?
like that all day when I can stand next to you?
你要是输了会怎么办?
What would you do if you lost?
你真是死咬着这个话题不放啊
You keep harping on this.
但我告诉你 我是输过竞选的
But I'll tell you something, I have lost elections.
我首次竞选国会议员时就输了
I lost the first time that I ran for Congress.
还被他们叫做赛琳娜·范德比尔特
They called me Selina Vanderbilt
好像那些范德比尔特还剩多少钱似的
as if the Vanderbilts had any money left.
不管怎样 在那之后 你也知道
Anyway, after that, you know,
我去了亚利桑那州的一个温泉浴场
I went to Arizona to a spa
我扪心自问 思考了几个棘手问题
and I took stock and I asked myself some tough questions...
等等  你是在那时候精神崩溃的吗?
Wait, is that when you had your nervous breakdown?
不不 我没有...
No, no, I did not...
不 我是去做温泉疗养 甜心
no, I went to a spa, sweetie.
因为当时你进精神病院了
No, when Rosa had to take care of me
不得不让罗莎来照顾我
because you went to a mental hospital.
不 亲爱的 我并没有进精神病院
No, darling, I didn't go to a mental hospital.
我去的是温泉浴场
I went to a spa.
你那电影就会这样把所有事都记录下来吗?
Is this how this is all going to be in your movie?
2017年1月3日
国会投票日
马瑟诸塞州支持赛琳娜·梅耶尔
Massachusetts votes for Selina Meyer.
- 11比10 奥布莱恩领先 - 我刚跟弗朗说了
- 11-10, O'Brien. - I just talked to Furlong.
梅耶:10 奥布莱恩:11
他说一切都在掌控之中
He said everything's under control plus a bunch of stuff
外加一堆菊花精液之辞 还有我可爱的嘴
about assholes and jizz and my pretty mouth.
理查德 乔纳在哪儿?
Richard, where is Jonah?
- 早上好! - 他妈的闭嘴 理查德
- Morning! - Shut the fuck up, Richard.
国会议员 乔纳 瑞安
新罕布什尔州
你可不能让邻居听到这话
Well, you can't scream that in this neighborhood.
我找不到自己的衣服了
I couldn't find my clothes.
不得不从她爸衣柜里找身衣服
I had to get this out of her dad's closet.
她原来说的是她在乔治敦大学读大四
She already told me she was a senior at Georgetown.
结果她指的是乔治敦日间学校
Turns out she meant Georgetown Day School.
她是数学竞赛队的
She's on the math team.
- 你在拍我? - 这可能算得上犯罪了
- Are you filming me? - Might be a crime.
哦对 凯瑟琳找我帮她
Oh, yeah, Catherine asked me
来拍摄竞选二三事
to help assist her with documenting the vote.
而且我还跟她学会怎么录像了
Plus she taught me how to make sure the camera is on.
好吧 真棒 那在这历史性的一天...
Oh, okay, good, well, then on this historic day...
- 还有 总统在线上 - 我操你妈的
- Also, the president's on the line. - Oh, motherfuck.
- 乔纳 听得到我吗? - 听得见 女士
- Jonah, can you hear me? - Yes, ma'am.
听我说 行吗? 你完了
You listen to me, all right? You are already dead.
你现在的一举一动都是为了你的家庭
What you do now you do for your family.
马上过来投票支持我!
You get yourself in there and you vote for me!
我整个总统任期
Is my entire presidency about to
都被伦尼议员掌控了吗?
have its neck snapped by Congressman Lennie here?
召集所有朋友 放缓此事
Call all friendlies. Let's slow this thing down.
第七修正案 总统选举平局决胜制
总票数
梅耶
奥布莱恩
国会议员 保罗 格雷夫斯
密歇根
伟大的密歇根州
The great state of Michigan
将投出自己的一票
would like to cast its vote.
但首先 请大家共同祈祷
But first, let us pray.
我母亲输掉了内华达州的重新计票
My mom lost the Nevada recount,
华盛顿邮报
总统平局决议提至国会
国会委员会
进入僵局
但更令人悲伤的消息是
but that was overshadowed by some terrible news.
讣告
凯瑟琳 卡尔弗特 伊顿
总统之母
我亲爱的外婆去世了
My dear mee-maw died.
这是美国总统办公室
This is the Oval Office.
2016年1月28日
三代梅耶女性齐聚一堂
Wow, three generations of Meyer women.
就像《鹰冠庄园》最棒的那集一样
It's like the best episode of "Falcon Crest" ever.
妈妈 这就是坚毅桌
Mother, this right here is the Resolute desk.
曾经罗斯福总统就在这张桌上办公
And it was used by FDR
现在轮到我 你女儿了 妈妈
and now by me, Mother, your daughter.
我衷心希望 你等头发长了
I do hope you'll wait till your hair grows
再去画画像
to have your portrait painted.
这有趣极了
This has been fun.
- 她看着就像个男的 - 好吧
- She looks like a boy. - Okay.
看着没那么深啊 你瞧
It doesn't seem that deep. Look.
2016年11月20日
凯瑟琳 伊顿葬礼
对 是没那么深
Oh, yeah, that's not that deep.
不好意思 这应该再埋深点吗?
Excuse me, should this be deeper?
你失去过祖父母吗?
Have you ever lost a grandparent?
我的祖父母们全都去世了
All my grandparents are dead.
丹 伊根
瑞安竞选经理
等等 不
Wait. Um, no.
也许有一两个还活着
One or two might still be alive.
2016年11月21日
距国会投票还有43天
很高兴重返华盛顿这美好的旧地
Good to be back in good old DC,
远离贪子 钱财 妓女
away from the greed, the money, and the hookers.
听着...
Listen, um...
... 所以 如果你待会儿没事的话...
...so, if you're not doing anything later...
耶稣操你大爷
Jesus fucking Christ.
让你妹妹别打电话给我了
You got to tell your sister to stop calling me.
美女
Hmm. Hey, girl.
作为一个不到40岁的从政人士
So now as a person in politics under 40,
艾米 布鲁克海默
梅耶总统高级顾问
你只是... 等下 停
you just... wait, cut.
事实上 只有我才能喊停
Actually, I'm the one that's supposed to say cut.
不不不 我喊停是因为我们得重来一遍
No, no, no, I'm saying it because we're starting that over.
好了吗? 开始
Ready? Action.
作为一个比大部分同行都要年轻的
As a person in politics
从政人士... 停 停
who's younger than most of her... cut, cut.
- 不 艾米 请别再喊... - 开始
- No, Amy, please don't actually say... - Action.
我们对中国领养制裁政策非常失望
We were really disappointed about the Chinese adoption sanctions.
2016年11月23日
距国会投票还有41天
但从好的方面来看
That... but on the bright side,
我把育儿室改造成独属我一人的男人天地
I turned the nursery into a man cave for me.
这有环绕立体音响 55寸的电视
I mean, surround sound, 55-inch television screen.
花的钱跟领养个孩子差不多 所以这事儿也解决了
It actually cost the same as the kid, so it works out.
我等不及要让温蒂来看了 她...
I can't wait for Wendy to see it. She is gonna...
也许会喜欢的吧
possibly like it.
- 你喜欢在白宫工作吗? - 喜欢 是的
- Do you like working at the White House? - I do, yes.
特工 马乔里 帕尔苗蒂
特务机关 总统安保
- 为总统工作愉快吗? - 愉快
- Have you enjoyed working for the president? - Yes.
- 你有为自己的生命担惊受怕过吗? - 没有
- Were you ever frightened for your life? - No.
- 你真的准备好为总统挡子弹了吗? - 是的
- Are you really ready to take a bullet for the president? - Yes.
- 你杀过人吗? - 无可奉告
- Have you ever killed a man? - Can't say.
你觉得我母亲是一位好总统吗?
Do you think my mom's a good president?
- 是 - 太棒了
- Yes. - That was perfect.
我采访的其他人
Everybody else that I've interviewed
都只顾着说自己
just talks about themselves all the time and...
你有空跟我一起吃个晚餐吗?
Um, would you like to have dinner with me sometime?
我... 好啊
Oh, yeah, I... I would love that.
我得说... 你知道我不是同性恋吧?
I should say that... you know that I'm not gay?
- 真的吗? - 是的 我...
- Really? - Yeah. Well, I...
- 我不是故意提起... - 对 不是
- I didn't mean that to come across... - No, it didn't.
我这么以为是因为
You know, it's just I assumed just because,
你的穿衣打扮 还有你盯着我看
you know, the way you dress and stare at me.
我喜欢男人
Well, I mean, I like guys.
议员希尔曼意外死亡
哈利·谢尔曼议员的感恩节之死
The Thanksgiving death of Congressman Harry Sherman
让在竞选中占据重要地位的新罕布什尔州重回竞选
put the key state of New hampshire back in play for the House vote.
谢尔曼死于沙门氏菌
我跟随在家乡竞选的乔纳·瑞安候选人
I followed candidate Jonah ryan as he campaigned in his home state.
2016年11月26日
距国会投票还有38天
我怎么样? 搞的妹子多到要拉出来阴蒂了
How am I doing? Eating so much pussy I'm shitting clit, son.
怎么了?
What?
这是小学!
This is an elementary school!
管管你喷粪的嘴  你个禽兽!
Watch your spewing mouth, you animal!
新汉普斯顿 纳舒厄
富兰克林 皮尔斯小学
你会付出代价的
Hey, you are gonna pay for that.
- 太侮辱人了 - 出去 出去
- That is assault. - Out. Out.
简直太侮辱人了 你们都是目击证人
That is assault. You are witnesses.
- 简直太侮辱人了! - 立刻出去
- This is assault! - Right now, get out.
大家好 我是乔纳·瑞安
Hello there. I'm Jonah Ryan.
乔纳 瑞安
竞选广告外景拍摄
我日
Ah, fuck.
你妈 食屎吧
Mothercunt. Piece of shit.
干 我日
Fuck you. Fuck you.
我日
Ah, fuck.
小心 小心 小心
Careful. Careful. Careful.
我觉得是因为你上肢无力
I think the problem is that you lack upper body strength.
我他妈为什么要砍柴啊?
Why am I even chopping the fucking wood?
都21世纪了
It's the 21st century.
我们都不用这狗屎玩意了
We don't even use this shit anymore.
用起来没问题啊
Worked fine.
我生长在这里
Ah, and I grew up right here
美丽的新罕布什尔州
in the awesome state of New Hampshire.
我载了一颗名叫乔纳·瑞安流星
I hitched my wagon to a shooting star named Jonah Ryan.
理查德 史培雷
瑞安竞选活动负责人
或许我应该说彗星
Well, maybe I should say comet
因为流星会燃净而他绝对不会
because shooting stars burn out and he never will.
唯一的坏处是我可能要得错过
The only downside is that I'll probably have to miss
吉尔伯特&沙利社团周年庆
my Gilbert & Sullivan Society annual show.
小歌剧就是我的热情所在
You know, operetta is my passion.
如果你想了解我们
If you want to know who we are
歌剧 日本天皇|2014年12月12日
樱花引蝶
我们是日本的绅士
We are gentlemen of Japan...
2017年1月3日
国会投票日
第七修正案 总统选举平局决胜制
总票数
梅耶
奥布莱恩
国会议员 保罗 格雷夫斯
密歇根
汽车故乡 又名美国金曲乌托邦
Home to Motown aka Hitsville USA,
投票给赛琳娜副总统
would like to cast its vote for President Selina...
凯瑟琳 梅耶
Catherine Meyer.
密歇根投票给塞琳娜·梅耶
Michigan votes for Selina Meyer.
- 天呐 理查德 开快点  - 明尼苏达?
- Jesus, Richard, please drive faster. - Minnesota?
如果你拿着摄像机
If you held the camera--
我不会拿那个摄像机的 理查德
I'm not gonna hold the camera, Richard.
我要怎么出现在摄像机里...
How would I be on the camera--
天呐 理查德 你差点杀了我
Jesus Christ, Richard! You could have killed me.
你就不能同时做两件简单的事情吗?
Can't you do two simple things at once?
感谢上帝 我没有撞到学生
I just thank God I didn't hit those schoolchildren.
谁管他们啊? 走! 走!
Who gives a fuck about them? Go! Go!
车发动不了了
Well, actually, the car won't start.
- 或许可以优步 - 我们不能优步
- Maybe call an Uber. - We can't call an Uber.
我因为评分太低被终生禁用了
I've been banned for life because I have a low rating.
密苏里弃权了
Missouri abstains from the vote.
- 密苏里弃权? - 弃权?
- Missouri abstained? - Abstained?
梅耶:12 奥布莱恩:12 弃权:1
汤姆干的
This is Tom and he's making a move
- 像那种神秘的象棋高手一样 - 好吧
- like some kind of grand fucking chess master. - Right.
和棋 卡尔波夫和卡斯帕罗夫的对决[象棋高手]
Stalemate his endgame. Shades of Karpov versus Kasparov.
你说的都是谁啊 肯特?
Oh, who's that for, Kent?
各位 密苏里要弃权
Guys, Missouri's gonna abstain.
汤姆只要保证没人能达到26票
Tom just needs to make sure that no one gets to 26
然后让他的老朋友
and then get his buddy
马伍德保证没人再投票了
Marwood to make sure there's not another vote.
- 就是这样 - 乔纳在哪  各位?
- That's it. - Where is Jonah, folks?
操! 他们在用来福打车?[打车软件]
Motherfucker! They're taking a Lyft now?
2016年12月2日
距国会投票还有32天
- 该起床啦 - 停
- Time to wake up. - Stop.
你个大拉拉
You big lesbo.
那你是什么? 该起床啦
And what's it to you? I think it's time to wake up.
突然之间我的生命有了意义
Suddenly everything in my life made sense.
其实我有个问题要问你
Actually, I got a question for you.
和你妈妈的双胞胎
Is it weird going hallway to hallway
- 双洞对接奇怪吗? - 什么?
- with your mom's twin? - What?
去 算了
To-- never mind.
如果我妈妈没有赢你会怎么办?
Do you think about what you'll do if my mother doesn't win?
本 卡佛蒂
总统梅耶的首席幕僚长
天 我也不知道 我还能干什么?
God, I have no idea. What else am I gonna do?
去世界各地看看?
Go out and see the world?
我甚至不喜欢看我的窗外 所以...
I don't even like looking out my window, so...
我真的...我不知道
I really-- I don't know.
本 你在家
Ben, you home.
我老婆
It's the spouse.
宝贝
Hey, sweetie.
乔伊斯 这是总统的女儿 凯瑟琳
Um, Joyce, this is the president's daughter Catherine.
凯瑟琳 这是我的老婆乔伊斯
Catherine, this is my wife Joyce.
- 很高兴见到你 - 惊喜啊
- Nice to meet you. - What a surprise.
我以为你和孩子们
I thought you and the kids were
- 这周去度假了 - 那是上个月的事情
- on vacation this week. - Yeah, that was last month.
乔伊斯在我第三次心脏病发作之后一直照顾我
Joyce, she took care of me after my third heart attack.
圣安德鲁医疗中心
我的第二任妻子也是个护士
My second wife was a nurse as well.
看来护士就是我的菜
I guess I have a thing for nurses, huh?
对 但我是他最好的护士
Yeah, but I his best nurse.
这些精美的小雕塑是非常好的投资
These Precious Moments figurines are a very good investment.
你要喝点什么吗?
Would you care for a drink?
我要找查理·贝尔德
Hi, I'm trying to reach Charlie Baird.
我是他的朋友  盖瑞·沃尔什
This is a friend of his, Gary Walsh.
关于... 关于什么?
Oh, what's the-- what is this concerning?
约会?
Um, hanging out?
你以前坐过摩托车吗?
没有
有空的时候我喜欢出去玩玩
所以我加入了一个俱乐部
这些都是我的同胞
These are my compatriots.
我们是一个历史悠久的西班牙语摩托车俱乐部
We are a historically Spanish-speaking motorcycle club
最近遭受了很多不公平的盘查
which has been under a great deal of unfair legal scrutiny lately.
这是我们的主席 卡韦萨
This is our president, El Cabeza.
你好 妹纸
Hola, chica.
嘿 停手
留着招呼洛佩兹兄弟吧!
我发现我加入后
I find that my involvement in the club
可以客观看待华盛顿这种两败俱伤的摩擦
keeps the internecine skirmishes of Washington in perspective.
2017年1月3日
国会投票日
你嚎
Yello.
- 你还有多远? - 我们在过安检
- Hey, how far out are you? - We're at security.
把那个汉普郡驼子给我带过来
Get the Hunchback of Notre Hampshire down to the floor.
我们这里有一点小骚乱
Well, we've reached a little bit of a kerfuffle.
可能比小骚乱再大一点
I'd say even more of a kerfuffle.
有点混乱  陷入泥藻
Like a snafu approaching quagmire.
乔纳·瑞安 谷歌我 谷歌我
Jonah Ryan. Just Google me. Google me.
- 麻溜的 谷歌我 - 冷静 先生
- Come on, fucking Google me. - Calm down, sir.
天呐
Jesus Christ.
不要!
No!
我们命悬一线了 但如果每个人都
We're hanging on by a thread, but if everyone votes
梅耶:13 奥布莱恩:13 弃权:1
按照我们预想的那样投票 我们就会赢
the way we think they're gonna vote, we'll win.
这只比"放心 只进去一点点"
Yeah, that's the least reassuring sentence
要让人心安一点
I've heard since "It's okay, it's just the tip."
看起来比威尔看"少棒闯天下"自撸时
It's looking tighter than Will's own butthole
不小心把手指
when he's got his finger jammed up there
插进菊花时还要紧
watching "Bad News Bears" while he jerks off.
- 到底是有多紧  威尔? - 非常紧 先生
- How tight is that, Will? - It's very tight, sir.
但是我暂时还不会把总统办公室卫生间的
Yeah, but I wouldn't take down the tampon dispenser
卫生棉售货机撤下来
in the Oval Office bathroom just yet.
如果我妈妈输了你怎么想?
How will you feel if my mom loses?
议员 罗杰 弗朗
俄亥俄州
如果你妈妈输了? 我会想她的
If your mom loses? I'll miss her.
她是一个优雅的女士
She's a pretty classy lady.
她是这里唯一真正懂我的人
She's the only person in this town who really gets me.
那我们明晚见
Oh, so I will see you tomorrow night.
国会投票战略研讨会|2016年12月14日
距国会投票还有20天
- 好的  - 好的
- Yes. - Yes, indeed.
随着票数越来越接近
As the vote got closer,
白宫内的氛围愈发紧张
the tension in the White House ratcheted up even further.
跑
Run.
门
Door.
汤姆他妈的想干什么?
So what the fuck is Tom up to?
抱歉 借过 抱歉
Sorry. Excuse me. I'm sorry.
怎么了?
Yes?
我只是看看是否还有关于我的会议
I was just checking to see if there was another meeting about me.
今天没有
Not today.
好的
Okay.
各位 迈克就是个智障 我的天
Guys, Mike is a moron. Jesus Christ!
- 我等不到就职典礼了 - 不行
- I can't wait until after the inauguration. - No.
他对其他智障来说是个启迪
I'm sure he's an inspiration to other slow adults,
我已经受够迈克了
but it's enough already with Mike.
我要开始准备采访了
I'll start lining up interviews.
自从代孕怀孕之后
Since the surrogate's pregnant,
男人窝又变回了宝宝窝
we've converted the man cave back into a baby cave.
电视已经挂在墙上了
And this thing here was already hard mounted.
非常结实
It's pretty solid,
所以我还是把它留在这吧
so I think I'm just gonna leave it here, you know?
这样还能给宝宝看教育片
That way, we can play educational stuff for the baby.
你懂的 巴尼 关于自然界的影片 没有不该看的
You know, Barney, nature films, nothing harmful.
天啊 我得记上 要检查铅含量
Oh, God, check for lead. Note to self.
冰球棍是怎么回事?
So what's up with all the hockey stuff?
国会舞会|2016年12月15日
距国会投票还有19天
进去吧 我们在这私聊 汤姆
Let's go in here. We can talk privately in here, Tom.
操
Shit.
我为此刻已经等了很久了
I've been waiting for this for a very long time.
好吧 你真蠢啊
Okay, how stupid are you,
- 你这奸诈小人  - 操
- you motherfucking snake? - Fuck.
- 好了 我要干你 - 这就对了!
- All right, I wanted to fuck you! - That's right!
今晚也要干我
And now you're trying to fuck me again tonight.
我今晚一定会干你!
No, I am fucking you tonight!
不 我要干你!
No, I'm gonna fuck you!
不 不 不 拜托
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, please.
你想过如果我妈输了你怎么办?
Have you thought about what you'll do if my mother loses?
国会舞会第二天早晨|2016年12月16日
距国会投票还有18天
我们会没事的
We'll be fine.
- 抱歉 - 嗯 就是这个沙发
- Sorry. - Yeah, hi. It's this couch right here, yeah.
不管我们是在白宫
I mean, whether we're in the White House
在查尔斯顿的古董店
or we're antiquing in Charleston
还是在巴布达岛的粉色沙滩上
or we're on the pink, sandy beaches of Barbuda,
我们都会没事的
you know, it's like we'll be fine.
- 你想放哪? - 别放这就好
- Where do you want this? - Just not here.
我们都还没去过意大利呢
We haven't even been to Italy.
我父亲是个海军
My father was a navy guy,
安德鲁 道尔
美国副总统
我们周游过世界
so we travelled the world quite a bit.
我非常高兴能成为国务卿
I am very excited to be secretary of state.
那格拉夫议员怎么办?
What about Congressman Graves?
我以为他才是国务卿
I thought that he was doing it.
不
No.
我有没有告诉你我有一张我父亲的照片?
did I tell you I have a photograph of my father?
2017年1月3日
国会投票日
- 新罕布什尔 - 他在哪?
- New Hampshire? - Where is he?
新罕布什尔州求议员施舍
The state of New Hampshire begs the floor's indulgence.
梅耶:14 奥布莱恩:13 弃权:1
我们的代表团仍缺一个人
We are still missing a member of our delegation.
- 你不是说他在保安处吗 - 他在啊
- I thought that you said he was at security. - He was.
他那么高 你们竟然能把他给整丢了
He's 18 feet tall. How could he have gone missing?
我的天 凯瑟琳 让开
Jesus. Catherine, move.
是另一个出口
Oh, other exit.
等等 不不不不不
Wait, no, no, no, no, no, no!
- 你要开门吗 不好意思 我来开 - 操
- Oh, you want it open? Sorry. Okay, I got it. - Fuck!
拜访马乔里父母|2016年12月22日
齐佩瓦族-克里 印第安人部落 蒙大拿
- 我太激动了
- I'm so excited.
她在吗?
She's here? Oh.
你好
Hi.
- 你好 妈 - 欢迎回来
- Hi, Mom. - Welcome home.
- 凯瑟琳 这是我父母 - 你好
- Catherine, this is my mom, my dad. - Hi.
- 你好 - 外公外婆
- Hi. Hi. - Grandma. Grandpa.
这是凯瑟琳·梅耶
This is Catherine Meyer,
- 我的工作上的朋友 - 什么
- my, uh, work friend. - What?
欢迎来到蒙大拿
Welcome to Montana.
我们吵架了
We had a fight.
我相信美国人民能做出正确的选择
I trust the American people to make the right decision.
2016年12月26日
距国会投票还有8天
如果他们做出了的选择
What if you think they're gonna make a certain decision
跟你所预想的的完全不同
and they make a different decision and then it completely derails
你会怎么办?
what you thought was gonna happen?
- 接着你的计划也变了 - 亲爱的 别哭啊
- And then your plans are different. - Oh, honey, don't cry.
妈妈会被选上的 亲爱的
Mommy's gonna get elected, honey.
我和马乔里分手了
Marjorie and I broke up.
太糟了
That's terrible.
- 你需要面纸吗? - 不 不用
- Do you need a tissue? - No, I'm fine.
你需要
Yeah, no, you do.
亲爱的 你看起来很糟糕
Honey. Oh, you look terrible!
你看起来很糟糕
You look terrible.
亲爱的 告诉你
Honey, let me tell you something.
马乔里很惹人烦 好吗?
Marjorie is insufferable, okay?
天涯何处无芳草啊 亲爱的
There are other-- there are other fish in the sapphic sea, babe.
真的
I mean, seriously,
特勤处都有很多女同
there are more lesbians in the Secret Service, even.
- 感觉好点了吗? - 好点了
- You feel better? - Yeah, a little bit.
好孩子 好了 继续吧
Good girl. Good. Okay, let's get back.
我关注的不是遗产
Legacy is not something that I can be concerned with.
我关注的是怎样尽全力
I'm laser-focused on doing the best possible job I can...
做好总统 凯瑟琳
as president-- Catherine.
不是谁都能进总统办公室的
Not everybody gets to just walk into the Oval.
2016年12月28日
距国会投票还有6天
总统女士
Madam President.
韦恩!
Wayne!
这是干什么? 你在做采访吗?
What the what? What, are you doing an interview?
是的
Yeah, he is.
- 我完全给忘了 - 好吧
- Well, completely slipped my mind. - Okay.
女士 这是今天下午的谈话要点
Ma'am, here are the talking points for this afternoon.
不 对不起
Oh, no. Sorry.
拿错了 马上回来
Wrong ones. I'll be back.
- 周三扑克桌见 - 好的
- See you at poker on Wednesday. - Right.
你看到我身边都是什么人了吧
So you see what I'm dealing with here.
所以你还没告诉他我取代了他是吗?
So you didn't tell him that I'm taking his job yet?
没有 那会是你的第一次新闻发布会
No, that'll be your first press release.
现在已经有了三个宝宝
Now that there will be three babies on the way,
我们决定把孩子们挪到楼上的主卧里去
we decided to move the kiddos upstairs to the master
这里将会成为新的爱巢
and this will be the new love palace.
她有梳妆台 我把这些挂在
She gets the dresser and I'll hang those
我也不知道放哪
in the-- I don't know where.
铅 还是个问题
The lead, still a problem.
请举起右手
Raise your right hand, please.
2017年1月2日
第115次美国国会宣誓
- 我庄重的起誓... - 我庄重的起誓...
- I do solemnly swear... - I do solemnly swear...
...我支持
...that I will support and
并维护美国国会的
defend the Constitution of the United States...
...我支持
...that I will support and
并维护美国国会的
defend the Constitution of the United States...
2017年1月3日
国会投票日
佛蒙特州弃权
Vermont abstains from the vote.
梅耶:20 奥布莱恩:21 弃权:2
我的天
Oh, God.
梅耶:20 奥布莱恩:21 弃权:3
已经有三票弃权 对不起 女士
That's three abstentions. Sorry, ma'am.
什么?
What?
等等 我们不能做什么吗?
Wait, though, isn't there anything that we can do?
不行 你得获得全票才能取胜
No, you'd have to run the table now to win.
我们不可能得到26票
There's no way you can get to 26.
但如果我们得到弗吉尼亚州的票呢?
But what if we get Virginia?
你拿不到那个州的票
You're not gonna get Virginia.
如果我们拿到西弗吉尼亚呢?
What if we get West Virginia?
你什么也得不到
You're not gonna get anything.
我们能给他们农业补贴吗?
Can we give them farm subsidies?
- 我们 - 你赢不了的 女士 你当不了总统了
- Can we-- - You can't win, ma'am. You're not gonna be president.
- 弗吉尼亚州投给了比尔·奥布莱恩 - 女士?
- Virginia votes for Bill O'Brien. - Ma'am?
弗吉尼亚州投给了比尔·奥布莱恩
Virginia votes for Bill O'Brien.
- 我天 比尔·奥布莱恩只有22票 - 没错
- Oh, Christ. O'Brien's only got 22. - Yeah.
他应该得不到26票
I mean, I don't think even he can get to 26.
看来汤姆·詹姆斯
Looks like we're looking
要成为总统了
down the barrel of a Tom James presidency.
你能再给我解释一下规则吗?
Could you explain to me one more time how this whole thing works?
为什么汤姆
Why is Tom--
我很抱歉 妈
I'm really sorry, Mom.
别着急 女士
Hey, don't worry, ma'am.
四年以后你还能再竞选
You can run again in four years, you know?
如果汤姆·詹姆斯当上总统的话就不行
Not if Tom James is president, I can't.
...华盛顿投给比尔·奥布莱恩
...Washington votes for Bill O'Brien.
华盛顿投给比尔·奥布莱恩
Washington votes for Bill O'Brien.
- 行了 大家都出去 - 好的
- All right, everybody clear out. - Okay.
- 出去! - 我们走吧
- Clear out! - Let's go.
除了你 艾米
Except you, Amy.
天啊 走吧 走吧
Oh, God, come on, come on.
好 听着
Okay, look.
现在给那个小人得志的乔纳打电话
Get that clowntard Jonah on the phone right now.
如果我们让他投给奥布莱恩呢?
What if we tell him to vote for O'Brien?
女士 你不能这么做 他是在野党...
Ma'am, you can't do that. He is the opposition--
这是我他妈唯一能做的事了 艾米
It is the only fucking thing that I can do, Amy.
真的
Seriously.
如果奥布莱恩赢得总统之位
If O'Brien wins the presidency,
我可以和他对着干四年
I can run against him in four years.
但如果汤姆·詹姆斯赢了
But if Tom James wins,
他就会当八年总统啊 艾米 八年
he's gonna be president for the next eight years, Amy. Eight!
12年 女士
12, ma'am.
汤姆的第一个任期不算在内
Tom's first term won't count
因为严格来说他会是晋升的副总统
because technically he'll be an elevated vice president.
但我听起来像肯特 所以
But I sound like Kent, so...
我的天啊 12年里
My God, in 12 years,
我会成为干瘪老太婆的
I'm gonna be a shriveled-up can of ass.
讲真 我不能 我的政治机会
Seriously, I can't-- I mean, my political window
会在我穿不了无袖裙的一刻关上
just slams shut the second I can't wear sleeveless dresses.
马上打电话给乔纳 让他投票给奥布莱恩
Call Jonah right now and tell him to vote for O'Brien.
打扰下 议院会议厅在哪儿?
Oh, excuse me. Where is the House Chamber?
议院会议厅在这边
The House Chamber is that way.
不 不是 我们刚...
No, it's not. We just--
我们刚他妈从那里过来
we just fucking came from there!
不 不是
No, it's not--
该死的
God damn it.
你最好是对的
You better be right.
他们要关闭投票了
They're gonna close the vote.
梅耶:21 奥布莱恩:25 弃权:3
- 奥布莱恩25票 - 他就差一票了
- O'Brien 25. - He's one away.
拜托 上帝 把约拿送到国会去
Please, God, deliver Jonah to Congress
然后随便给他个癌症 我不在乎
and then give him any kind of cancer. I don't care.
- 马乔里? 我不想和你说话 - 我很抱歉
- Marjorie? I don't want to talk to you. - I'm sorry, okay?
我和父母说了咱俩的事
I told my parents about us.
- 新罕布什尔州... - 他们接受不了 但我不在乎
- New Hampshire... - They took it hard, but I don't care.
- 我爱你 -...自豪地投票给
- I love you. - ...proudly casts its vote
- 塞琳娜·梅耶总统 - 我也爱你
- for President Selina Meyer. - I love you, too.
新罕布尔州投给塞琳娜·梅耶
New Hampshire votes for Selina Meyer.
投票到此结束
The vote is hereby closed.
结果是奥布莱恩25票 梅耶22票
That's O'Brien 25, Meyer 22.
第七修正案 总统选举平局决胜制
总票数
弃权
梅耶
奥布莱恩
三票弃权 没有候选人获得
With three abstentions, no candidate has received
宪法要求的26票
the constitutionally required 26 votes.
议会休会
This House is adjourned.
抱歉 我想改投
I'm sorry, I would like to change my vote.
我选错人了
I voted for the wrong person.
我想改投 谢谢
I would like to change my vote, thank you.
大家去哪儿?
Where is everyone going?
来自新罕布尔州的先生
The gentleman from New Hampshire
申请重投 谢谢
puts forth onto the floor a do-over, thank you.
我们刚刚在众议院见证了一次
We have just witnessed a historic no decision
历史性的无结果投票
in the House of Representatives.
好了 我们得发表一个声明
Okay, we got to get a statement out.
参议院现在将
The Senate will now choose
在汤姆·詹姆斯和劳拉·蒙特兹之间选择
between Senators Tom James and Laura Montez.
- 马乔里 - 你好 女士
- Oh, hey, Marjorie. - Hello, ma'am.
输了就是输了
If I lose, I lose.
泰迪·罗斯福输过 约翰·亚当斯输过
Teddy Roosevelt lost. John Adams lost.
温斯顿·丘吉尔输过
Winston Churchill lost.
很多总统都输过
So plenty of presidents have lost
然后继续着非常伟大的事业
and gone on to do great, great things.
拍完了吗? 亲爱的
Are we done, sweetie?
- 我不能输 - 你不会输的 不会
- I can't fucking lose this thing. - You won't. You won't.
现在我们走进红厅
We are now entering the Red Room,
红厅最初是黄色的
which originally was the yellow drawing--
总统女士 我很抱歉
Madam President, I am so sorry.
- 我们刚来 - 没事的
- We're just coming through. - Oh, no, it's fine.
大家都进来 进来吧
Everybody come on in. Come on in.
欢迎 欢迎
Welcome, welcome.
欢迎 你好
Welcome. Hello.
看看你 我觉得你来自堪萨斯州
Look at you. I think you're from Kansas.
- 我能看出... - 没错 我投给您了两次
- I can see it-- - I am. I voted for you twice.
今年还有您第一次竞选总统时
This year and back when you ran for president the first time.
你捂着包好像我要偷走一样
Oh, you're clutching your bag like I'm gonna steal it.
没有!
Oh, no!
- 你想照张相吗? - 好啊
- Would you like to take a picture? - Oh, yeah.
她知道自己要什么
Oh, yeah. She knows what she wants.
- 照了吗? - 嗯
- Did we get it? - Yeah.
很好 谢谢
Okay, great. Thank you.
我爱你
I love you.
谢谢
Thank you.
还有想要合照的吗?
Who else would like a photo?
有人说平局就像在亲你的姐妹
Some say a tie is like kissing your sister.
棕榈滩 佛罗里达
凯瑟琳 伊顿 动物救助中心
但我花了一个总统选举团的平局
But it took an electoral college tie
才亲到了那个我不知道的姐妹
for me to get to kiss the sister I never knew I had.
凯瑟琳 梅耶出品
我只是想问问你对于
I'm just gonna ask you what you think
我母亲管理团队中一些人的看法
of a few people in my mother's administration.
这是个很好的机会 谢谢
It's a great opportunity. Thank you.
你觉得艾米·布鲁克海默如何
What do you think of Amy Brookheimer?
她喜欢听到自己说话
She likes to hear herself talk.
- 紧张 - 刺耳
- Tense. - Shrill.
- 刺耳 - 刺耳
- Shrill. - Shrill.
- 刺耳 - 他们说刺耳了吗?
- Shrill. - Did they say shrill?
- 你如何描述盖瑞·沃尔什? - 善良的人
- How would you describe Gary Walsh? - A kind person.
- 卡车铺的寻欢洞 - 可以倒立不动
- Truck stop glory hole. - Can do a handstand still.
- 你认为丹·伊根怎么样? - 傻逼
- What do you think of Dan Egan? - Douchebag.
- 寻欢洞的另一边 - 他人不错
- The other side of the glory hole. - He's fine.
麦克是白痴 他能拿驾照真是奇迹
Mike is an idiot. It's amazing he got a driver's license.
我人生中遇到过的
One of the most extraordinarily
最奇葩的人之一
incoherent people I've ever met in my life.
有时在一部未来主义电影 一部科幻片中
Sometimes, like, in a futuristic-- like a sci-fi movie,
你会看到一个机器人
you'll see, like, a robot
他就像那种让你为之难过的
that's like the old version of the robot
- 老机器人 - 乔纳呢?
- and you kind of feel bad. - How about Jonah?
乔纳·瑞安是新罕布尔州应有的
Jonah Ryan is the congressman
国会议员
that the people of New Hampshire deserve.
你觉得自己作为副总统成就显著吗?
Do you think you had a crowning achievement as vice president?
我成了总统
Well, I became president.
- 这算是成就吧? - 你投票给妈妈了吗?
- Can we call that an achievement? - Did you vote for Mom?
如果我投了
If I would have voted,
我肯定会投给你妈的
it would have certainly been for your mother.
你们认为自己20年后会怎样?
Where do you see yourself in 20 years?
- 白宫 - 我会在加拉巴哥群岛[位于厄瓜多尔西部]
- White House. - I'd say the Galapagos Islands.
- 成为总统 - 我
- Just be president. - I
在2036年的计划里标好了 我会去那里
have it penciled in 2036. Gonna go there.
- 登上权利的王座 - 我买了两张票
- Just the seat of power. - I bought two tickets.
不知道另一个人会是谁
I don't know who the other is gonna be,
但我猜到时候我会有伴儿的
but I'm assuming by then I'll be coupled up.
大家都说 "总统先生 这是被签入法律中
Everyone saying, "Mr. President, this is the most important bill
最重要的法案"
that has ever been signed into law."
我想靠近太阳
I like to be close to the sun.
我没想那么远
I haven't thought that far ahead.
我太专心于当下了
I'm so focused on the present.
我问你一个问题
Let me ask you a question.
最好的女同色情网站是哪个?
What's the best lesbian porn site?